quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "How many possible keys exist in a cryptographic algorithm that uses 6-bit encryption keys?",
        "correct_answer": "64",
        "options": ["32", "12", "16", "64"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following sequences properly describes the TCP three-way handshake?",
        "correct_answer": "SYN, SYN/ACK, ACK",
        "options": ["SYN, ACK, SYN/ACK", "PSH, RST, ACK", "SYN, SYN/ACK, ACK", "SYN, RST, FIN"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of malware is Marshall likely dealing with?",
        "correct_answer": "Worm",
        "options": ["Logic bomb", "Trojan Horse", "Virus", "Worm"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What technology should Mary use for an open-source authentication, authorization, and accounting server for wireless network services?",
        "correct_answer": "RADIUS",
        "options": ["RADIUS", "XTACAS", "TACACS+", "OAuth"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a mode of operation for the Data Encryption Standard?",
        "correct_answer": "AES",
        "options": ["CBC", "AES", "CFB", "OFB"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In a scenario with a missing patch in a company's web application, what is the threat?",
        "correct_answer": "Malicious hacker",
        "options": ["Unpatched web application", "Web defacement", "Malicious hacker", "Operating system"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What security management does the process of code moving to the production environment describe?",
        "correct_answer": "Change management",
        "options": ["Regression testing", "Code review", "Change management", "Fuzz testing"]
    },
    {
        "question": "STRIDE, PASTA, and VAST are all examples of what type of tool?",
        "correct_answer": "Threat modelling methodologies",
        "options": ["Risk assessment methodologies", "Control matrices", "Threat modelling methodologies", "Awareness campaign tools"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What Kerberos service generates a new ticket and session keys and sends them to the client?",
        "correct_answer": "TGS",
        "options": ["KDC", "TGT", "AS", "TGS"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What principle of information security states that an organisation should implement overlapping security controls whenever possible?",
        "correct_answer": "Defence in depth",
        "options": ["Least privilege", "Separation of duties", "Defence in depth", "Security through obscurity"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of facility is being used by David's company in the event of a disaster?",
        "correct_answer": "Cold site",
        "options": ["Hot site", "Mobile site", "Cold site", "Warm site"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the final step of a quantitative risk analysis?",
        "correct_answer": "Conduct a cost/benefit analysis",
        "options": ["Assess the annualised rate of occurrence", "Conduct a cost/benefit analysis", "Determine asset value", "Derive the annualised loss expectancy"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SNMP use?",
        "correct_answer": "161",
        "options": ["119", "123", "143", "161"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does IMAP use?",
        "correct_answer": "143",
        "options": ["119", "123", "143", "161"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does NTP use?",
        "correct_answer": "123",
        "options": ["143", "123", "119", "161"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does NNTP use?",
        "correct_answer": "119",
        "options": ["161", "143", "119", "123"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does HTTP use?",
        "correct_answer": "80",
        "options": ["80", "8080", "443", "5555"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does DNS use?",
        "correct_answer": "53",
        "options": ["53", "68", "80", "52"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SMTP use?",
        "correct_answer": "25",
        "options": ["37", "53", "25", "27"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does SSH use?",
        "correct_answer": "22",
        "options": ["21", "22", "23", "24"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does FTP command control use?",
        "correct_answer": "21",
        "options": ["21", "22", "19", "20"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What port does FTP data transfer use?",
        "correct_answer": "20",
        "options": ["21", "22", "20", "19"]
    }
    
]